nicereply.com 2019-04-29

# Privacy policy | Customer Satisfaction Survey, NPS & CES

## Privacy Policy and Cookies

This privacy policy (the **Privacy policy​** ) describes the processing of your personal data by Nice Reply, s.r.o., with its registered office at Štefanovičova 2971/8, 811 04 Bratislava, the Slovak Republic, ID No. 46 682 007, registered with the Commercial Register of District Court Bratislava I, Section Sro, Insert No. 81612/B (the **Company​** , **we** or **us** ) for the purpose of providing you with our services located at https://www.nicereply.com/ (the **Site​** ) consisting of customer satisfaction assessment (the **Services​** ). 

### WHAT KIND OF INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?

We collect the following information (the **Data** ​) about you, depending on you use of our Site and/or Services: 

#### A. Information necessary for the purpose of registration and access to our Site

For the purpose of registration on our Site and further access to our Site and personalized services on our Site we process the following information: (i) your name, (ii) surname and (iii) e-mail. 

The processing of the above information is necessary for the performance of the contract entered into between you and us. The legal basis of processing these information is Article 6(1)(b) of the GDPR regulation. 

#### B. Information necessary for the provision of Services

For the purpose of providing our Services (i.e. the provision of your paid services) we process the following information: (i) your name, (ii) surname, (iii) address, (iv) e-mail, (v) information about you payment card (card number, expiry date and CVV code). 

The processing of the above information is necessary for the performance of the contract entered into between you and us. The legal basis of processing these information is Article 6(1)(b) of the GDPR regulation. 

#### C. Information collected for marketing purposes

For the purpose of receiving our news and/or newsletters, information of sales, actualizations, updates and offers and other marketing materials in the form of e-mails or letters and/or notifications we process (i) your name, (ii) surname, (iii) e-mail and (iv) address. 

We process these personal data on the basis of your express consent. The legal basis of processing these information is Article 6(1)(a) of the GDPR regulation. 

If you decide that you do not wish to receive such messages, you have the right to withdraw your consent by clicking on the following hyperlink directly in our e-mail communication or available directly in your account in section **personal settings​**. The withdrawal of your consent may resulting in you not receiving information on sales, actualizations, updates and offers. It is not possible to withdraw your consent with receiving emails containing notifications regarding the provision of Services. 

#### D. Information collected while using our Site

For the purpose of continuous improvement of our Services, developing your user experience when using our Site we process the following information: (i) about your computer, (ii) about your visit and usage of our Sites and/or our Services (including your IP address and geographical location, browser type and version, operating system, referral source, length of visit, page views and website navigation paths or any similar information that may be obtained by the Company directly or indirectly from third party providers.), (iii) generated in the course of the use of those Services (including the timing, frequency and pattern of Service use). 

The processing of the above information is necessary for the performance of the contract entered into between you and us. The legal basis of processing these information is Article 6(1)(b) of the GDPR regulation. 

#### E. Information published on your profile

Fur the purpose of creating a profile on or Site we process your following personal data: (i) name, (ii) surname and (iii) e-mail. 

The processing of the above information is necessary for the performance of the contract entered into between you and us. The legal basis of processing these information is Article 6(1)(b) of the GDPR regulation. 

#### F. Information we receive when you communicate with us

For the purpose of communicating with us for any reason (for example, support when using our Site/ Services, resolving complaints and any other problems etc.) we shall process your following personal data: (i) your name, (ii) surname, (iii) address, (iv) e-mail, (v) phone number, (vi) communication content, (vii) metadata associated with the communication and (viii) any other necessary data, which you shall decide to provide in your communication. 

The processing of the above information is necessary for the performance of the contract entered into between you and us. The legal basis of processing these information is Article 6(1)(b) of the GDPR regulation. 

#### ON WHAT BASIS DO WE PROCESS YOUR DATA?

In addition to legal basis mentioned above, we may process any Data to comply with our statutory obligations pursuant to Article 6(1)(c) GDPR or to protect our legitimate interests pursuant to Article 6(1)(f) GDPR, for example in cases of fraud prevention, network and information security, direct marketing purposes. 

We shall process your Data in accordance with applicable law and protect your Data against misuse and/or any unlawful disclosure. 

#### HOW DO WE SHARE YOUR DATA?

In relation to your use of our Site and/or Services (and, if circumstances so require), we may disclose your Data (and you agree with such disclosure) in accordance with the minimization principle to a limited number of persons such as our employees, contractors, officers, professional advisers, agents, suppliers or member of our group of companies insofar as reasonably necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy, mainly with the following legal entities: (i) [Braintree Payments​](https://www.braintreepayments.com/). 

We may disclose your personal information: (i) to the extent that we are required to do so by law, (ii) in connection with any ongoing or prospective legal proceedings or (iii) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk). 

Non-Personally Identifiable Information: We may share non-personally identifiable information (such as anonymous usage data, referring/exit pages and URLs, platform types, number of clicks, etc.) with interested third parties to help them understand the usage patterns for certain services. 

We do not share your personally identifiable information or personally-identifiable location information with third-party companies for their direct marketing use. 

#### DO WE TRANSFER YOUR DATA TO THIRD COUNTRIES?

The Data that we collect may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which we operate in order to achieve the purpose of the processing and/or collecting provided for in this Privacy Policy. For the same purpose, your Data may be transferred across the European Union and/or European Economic Area and countries that according to the European Commission ensure an adequate level of protection as published from time to time by the Office for Personal Data Protection at its website: _https://dataprotection.gov.sk/uoou/en/content/transfer-third-countries-ensuring-adequate-level-protection_

#### FOR HOW LONG SHALL WE BE PROCESSING YOUR DATA?

Except as provided otherwise by law, we shall be authorized to process your Data in a form which permits your identification for no longer than is necessary for the purposes for which the personal data are processed (that may include the time when you continue to use our Site and/or Services and/ or the whole time during which the purpose of processing your Data continues), if not stated otherwise, for the following period: 

#### A. Information necessary for the purpose of registration and access to our Site

We shall process information necessary for the purpose of registration and access to our Site from the day on which you register on our Site and 90 days following your unregistration. During this period (90 days following unsubscription) we shall process your data only for the purpose of terminating the contractual relationship, established by your registration on our Site, between you and us, for resolving any disputes, which arose from this relationship and protection of our legitimate interests. 

#### B. Information necessary for the provision of Services

We shall process information necessary for the provision of Services as of the day you order the Service until its full provision (i.e. until the day on which the Service shall be provided to you and the price of such Service shall be paid). 

#### C. Information collected for marketing purposes

We shall process information collected for marketing purposes as of the day your provide us your consent until (i) your withdrawal of the consent or (ii) you unsubscribe from our Site. 

#### D. Information collected while using our Site

We shall process information collected while using our Site as of the day when you visit our Site for the first time until you unsubscribe from our Site. 

#### E. Information published on your profile

We shall process information published on your profile as of the day you publish you information on your profile until you unsubscribe from our Site. 

#### F. Information we receive when you communicate with us

We shall process information we receive when you communicate with us as of the day we receive them from you until we handle your request resulting from our e-mail communication. 

We shall be authorised to process your Data after you stop using our Site and/or Services or after you withdraw your consent, if it is necessary to (a) meet our legal obligations or (b) establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk). 

#### WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS AND OBLIGATIONS?

You are entitled to:

#### Access to your Data

In particular to: (i) request information about the purpose of their processing, (ii) categories of processed Data, (iii) identifying the recipient to whom the Data are to be provided, and (iv) duration of processing and collecting your Data. 

#### Correction of your Data

In case you acknowledge that we are processing Data about you, which are not correct, please inform us about this matter and we shall correct such uncorrect data without undue delay. 

#### Erasure of your Data (Right to be forgotten)

We shall erase your Data if: (i) the Data are no longer necessary in relation to the purpose for which they were collected, (ii) you withdraw your consent to processing your Data according to this Privacy Policy, (iii) you object to the processing of your Data, (iv) in case your Data have been obtained by us unlawfully, (v) we have a legal obligation to do so and (vi) the Data have been collected in relation to the offer of information society services. 

#### Restriction of Data processing

You have the right to restriction of your Data processing if: (i) the accuracy of your Data is contested by you for a period which shall enable us to verify the accuracy of your Data, (ii) the processing of your Data is unlawful and you request restriction of such Data use instead of erasure, (iii) we no longer need your Data for the purpose of processing, but are required by you for the establishment, exercise or defence of legal claims, and (iv) you have objected to the processing of your Data pending the verification whether our legitimate grounds override yours. 

#### Data portability

You are entitled to receive your Data processed by us in a structured, commonly used and machine-readable format for the purpose of transmitting such Data to another data controller. 

#### Object Data processing

You have the right to object the processing of your Data based on the grounds of legitimate interest, marketing purposes, profiling related to direct marketing. 

#### Lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority

If you consider that your rights relating to the processing of your Data have been infringed you have the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority. 

#### DO WE PROCESS DATA OF CHILDREN?

Protecting the privacy of young children is especially important. For that reason, we do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 16. If you are under 16, please do not send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 16 is allowed to provide any personal information to or on the Site. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 16 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 16, please contact us at contact@nicereply.com. 

#### HOW ARE FINANCIAL TRANSACTIONS PROCESSED?

All the financial transactions process at our Site and/or in respect of the Services are handled through our payment services provider Braintree Payments. You can review the provider's privacy policy at https://www.paypal.com/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full. We will share information with our payment services provider only to the extent necessary for the purposes of processing payments you make via our Site, refunding such payments and dealing with complaints and queries relating to such payments and refunds. 

#### HOW DO WE COOPERATE WITH THIRD PARTY WEBSITES?

Our Site includes hyperlinks to, and details of, third party websites. We have no control over, and are not responsible for, the privacy policies and practices of third parties. 

#### DO YOU HAVE ADDITIONAL QUESTIONS?

Should you require any clarifications or additional information regarding Data processing or protection, including the case if you wish to exercise any of the rights set out in this Privacy Policy, please contact us via email at contact@nicereply.com. 

#### HOW DO WE UPDATE OUR PRIVACY POLICY?

We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy. If we change our privacy policies and procedures, we will post those changes on the Site to keep you aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances we may disclose it. It is important that you review this Privacy Policy regularly to ensure you are updated as to any changes.

#### WHAT KIND OF COOKIES DO WE USE?

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser on your mobile device or computer to identify you (usually based on an anonymous identifier). The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server in order to identify your visit to a particular page, the list of ads you have responded to, the type of browser you are using, and also to remember information you have filled it on our website. 

We use cookies to personalise content and ads to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about use of our Site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners who may combine it with other information that you’ve provided to them or that they’ve collected from your use of their services. 

The purpose of using Cookies is to be able to adapt to your needs, to distinguish you from other users, to prevent the display of irrelevant ads in your web browser and to prevent the need for your repeated login to our Interface. 

Cookies may be either "persistent" cookies or "session" cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed. 

There are also third-party Cookies: ​Third-party cookies are cookies that are set by a website other than our Site. For example, a website might have a social media like button on their site. That like button will set a cookie that can be read by social media provider. The aim of third-party cookies is often to collect certain information to carry out various research into behaviour, demographics and not least for targeted marketing etc. 

Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

We use both session, persistent and third-party cookies on our Site and/or with respect of our Services. According to different purpose, there are other subcategories we may use. In the list below, you can find all cookies we use on Our Interface: 

##### Processes

Processes cookies enable our site to provide services in accordance with your expectations. For example, navigation on the website or access to secure areas of the site. Without these cookies we shall not be able to provide you with fully fledged services on our site.   
---  
Name | Provider | Purpose | Validity | Type  
userId | Nicereply | Client identification | 10 years | Persistent  
ratingUserId | Nicereply | Rating client identification | 10 years | Persistent  
ratingBrowserId | Nicereply | Browser identification | 10 years | Persistent  
  
##### Preferences

These files allow your internet browser to remember the information that affect the appearance and/ or behaviour of the website. This shall include information about your language selection, currency used and territory in which you are located.   
---  
Name | Provider | Purpose | Validity | Type  
awards-app-popup | Nicereply | Status of popup windows for awards | 1 year | Persistent  
cookie-agreement | Nicereply | Cookie confirmation status | 1 year | Persistent  
  
##### Security

We use security cookies to verify your identity when logging in, to prevent fraudulent use of your login information and to prevent your user data from unauthorized access.   
---  
Name | Provider | Purpose | Validity | Type  
sid | Nicereply | Client identification |  | Session  
  
##### Analytics

We use these cookies for analytical purposes. Their purpose is to monitor the traffic on our Interface, its individual parts and the frequency of its use.   
---  
Name | Provider | Purpose | Validity | Type  
Google Analytics | Google | Session google analytics | 2 years | Persistent  
LinkedIn | LinkedIn | Advertising | 6 months | Persistent  
Facebook | Facebook | Advertising | 3 months | Persistent  
Twitter Advertising | Twitter | Advertising | 2 years | Persistent  
  
Please acknowledge that blocking and/or deleting cookies will have a negative impact upon the usability of the Site and/or our Services.
